Eugene Buinouski

Middle DevOps Engineer

CONTACT INFO

Eugene.Buinouski@outlook.com

in Linkedin.com/in/eugene-buinouski

? Tbilisi, Georgia

EDUCATION

Belarusian State University

Radiophysics

SPOKEN LANGUAGES LEVELS

Russian: Native English: B1-B2

PROFILE

DevOps Engineer with 5+ years of experience in providing maintenance and support for different systems and services, automation of any administrative processes, ensuring system security, fixing security threats, developing CI/CD according GitOps concept, developing python scripts for automation, troubleshooting of environment, advising development teams on the implementation of CI/CD pipelines. Looking for a DevOps job. I can start on June 1st.

EXPERIENCE

Elinext Sep. 2022 - Now Tbilisi, Georgia

DevOps Engineer

Migration to GCP, developing CI/CD pipelines according GitOps concept, maintenance, developing python scripts for automation, troubleshooting of environment, docker, pipeline issues, consulting development teams on implementation of CI/CD pipelines, developing and implementing Ansible playbooks, security consulting, creation and mentoring cloud technology training.

Used frameworks and technologies:

AWS, GCP, Azure, Python, Docker, Docker-Compose, K8s, Ansible,

Jenkins, Gitlab CI/CD, GitHub Actions

Forbase Nov. 2018 - Nov. 2021

Minsk, Belarus

System Administrator Organization of backups: sites, IIS settings, various directories,

configurations and virtual machine data. Up-to-date system and firmware support, high availability support. Monitoring and notification of: system, equipment, availability, integrity and safety of backups. System

configuration, services and roles. Prevention of critical events. Troubleshooting. Infrastructure planning and implementation. Automation of

administrative processes.

Used frameworks and technologies:

Windows Server, MS SQL, AWS (EC2, S3), Dell PowerEdge/PowerVault,

Synology NAS, Ipswitch WhatsUp Gold

Forbase Feb. 2017 - Nov. 2017 **System Administrator** Internship.

Minsk, Belarus

Used frameworks and technologies:

Windows Server, MS SQL, Synology NAS, Ipswitch WhatsUp Gold

PROJECTS

Elinext Feb. 2023 - Now **Security consult**

Security consult

Responsibilities: Consulting and configuring security solutions.

Elinext

Elinext Cloud Training

Oct. 2023 - Now Internal cloud technology training

Responsibilities:

Creating and mentoring AWS cloud technology training.

Elinext

Sat.io Jun. 2023 - Oct. 2023

Satellite managing project.

Responsibilities:

Implementing CI/CD pipelines, advising development teams on the implementation of CI/CD pipelines, resolving issues of containerization.

Elinext

Elinext Gateway Mar. 2023 - Jun. 2023 Internal corporate network.

Responsibilities:

Developing and implementing Ansible playbooks for automated server

configuration.

Elinext **Broadcom DX**

Monitoring and analysis application. Sep. 2022 - Feb. 2023

Responsibilities:

Migration to GCP, developing CI/CD, maintenance, developing python

scripts for automation.

Forbase Marketing G2

Oct. 2018 - Nov. 2021 Marketing solution for social media

Forbase Safetypay

Nov. 2018 - Nov. 2021 Solution for payment methods

Forbase Marketing G2

Feb. 2017 - Nov. 2017 Marketing solution for social media

SKILLS

AWS EC2 / Route 53 / S3 / VPC / Beanstalk / ECS / ECR / EKS / RDS /

DevTools / SNS / Cloud Formation / Cloud Watch

GCP Compute / GKE / Storage

CONTAINER Docker / Docker-Compose / Swarm **TOOLS**

DEVOPS GitLab CI/CD / GitHub Actions / Jenkins / Ansible / Git / K8s **TOOLS**

LINUX CentOS / RHEL / Fedora / Debian / Ubuntu / Networking (iptables, L2TP,

SERVER WireGuard, etc.) AD DC / GPO / DNS / DHCP / IIS / Hyper-V / DFS / Failover cluster /

Synology NAS / Dell PowerEdge / Dell PowerVault

WINDOWS SERVER WSUS

VIRTUAL Hyper-V / VMware(vSphere)

TOOLS

MONITORING Ipswich WhatsUp Gold / Zabbix

SCRIPTING Python / Bash / PowerShell

OTHERS DELL (OME, OMSA, iDRAC) / Network Security / GitOps

PERSONALITY

Experimenting with new technologies and frameworks, continuous learning, resolving the most difficult problems, choosing the most appropriate technologies, flexible and organized.

HOBBIES

STORAGE

Programming, radio electronics, CTF.